There's Gotti, okay. Well, he's banned we've banned
Yeah
I just wanted to come up here and first say that they use that picture. That's a photoshop picture of CB
I think you guys know who that is CB
She has a lot of nudes going around and they've been photoshopping my face onto it because like I said I also have haters
So sorry they did that to you. That's because they don't like me
Okay, they use the name Hanna. They use the name Hanna and then they put up that
I mean that's obviously not Hanna. Hanna is a nice person, but they don't like her either, so they don't like me or her
So they're gonna, if you ever see me or her come up here
Yeah, it's a good idea to use a screen for sure because they'll try it with my name too, no doubt
But I want everyone to know that's not my body. There are no news of me out here. It's CB
Yeah, they can put like anybody's head on a new body so easily these days. So, you know
Yeah, it was a it was a scandal. They were trying to push their narratives and whatnot. You know how it goes
Listen, I've been embroiled in some shit
Maybe maybe we'll learn what you'll learn about it someday
But all right, I just wanted to clear that up and like I said make sure when Hannah or I come up
I would highly recommend using the screen
All right, take care. Well
I mean, it's like it's someone's bit like it's one gets banned. Why do they want to be here?
I mean, it's like or they are how much just like, you know
JT can contact me and try to talk it out on just quarter, but he said something, you know
Disrespectful of God. He has a channel and people are saying things in his chat about him
Can he ban them or no or he's supposed to just take the disrespect
So yeah, so I just it's my fault this you know, I just say oh, oh here's Hannah
I know and then it's like you know, but at the same time. It's not a big deal. Just delete the stream
Yeah, CB is JT. Yeah
Isn't that something I mean, it's just it's crazy. It's definitely my every time I heard body TV you were oh my gosh
CB
Well, it's like, you know, it's like now that they're
pulling balling with other people, it's like, it has
become so complicated, like a weird, it's weird.
Like, first of all, I would just never even have a, you
know, ran a picture, pictures of random people on my phone.
That's kind of weird.
Or Photoshop pictures, and then you're sending them to
panels and chasing people around panel.
It just seems like it's insane.
Okay.
It's just
Very nice to be so that's what the book says be kind like I mean it's like
A city or God your rest these handy work. Oh, you know aren't they aren't they just aren't they just brilliant or very creative people
Sit on Photoshop and play with you know people's pictures
And it's a big time like wait, you know, you're not a criticize me some more say I say I'm I'm I'm working with like
These people are trying to like, you know, threaten people. Please
You're gonna you're gonna sit in a whine at me. You're just don't whine at me, please don't whine
Why do you why are you saying? I'm I'm in on all this and I'm like
Talk about something else. But that's what you said. Oh, I I'm in their hands. No, I'm not in there
I'm my own person. Sometimes I've let people talk more than they
I don't know you're talking about
I'm trying to show this. Oh
Crystal crystal, but if I said that crystal it's obviously a joke because you know you're you look nothing like her
But I don't
Don't know how that would ever come. I don't know. I
Don't know just play the plate on Sam and I'll take a look
Thank you. You'll speak when you come up. I'll tell okay
Okay. Thank you
Thank you, okay, thank you Hannah, so I'll know from now on yeah
No, whatever whatever whatever crystal, you know, you know, it looks like him. So it's like what what it's like a ridiculous
It's like it's like it's one ridiculous comparison that did it's like not even
That's why I don't think I would say that because it's like so it's not even like
You know got a bigger dick than me up and send to the psyche
I'll take a gander
I mean like shit. I gotta see you dude. It got a bigger dick than mr. Big Place, but I doubt it
Well
I don't know, I don't know. I think there might have been a salami in your in your jock. I'm not sure. It was
I didn't see I didn't see skin. You can show it. I mean, it's kind of safer work, dude. I
don't I just don't want to show like a
Semi semi on my show
I don't know
It is nice, you know
Instagram
Like you be like
my mouth is getting tired.
Oh my God.
Well, this is just what you gave me.
I feel like I got to keep my job.
Crystal, it sounds like it was maybe like not,
maybe I tried to make it,
I don't remember saying that,
but it wasn't serious, it was just, you know.
It's kind of like
People but I don't like nothing dictated. I'm not like anything they try to like hurt people's feelings
Okay
Like I make love with they like I just I don't put it all the way in at all
Well, thank you for letting me know
So, okay, so the reason
Okay, he's married and he might remember. Oh, okay. Oh, you know
You know, he's I mean, he's it's fine. No one has
Yeah, yeah
I'm trying to hit the like this or not in that but like the G spot like try to get up top like, you know
Put like two fingers in
And go for the top
There's like kind of a divot
Yeah, but I do like touching the cervix for real and guys because mr.. Big pipes comes on the person keeps saying
Oh, they're giving me all these dislikes. So if you can hit the light for me, you don't mind
Fucking he thinks like fucking vaginas are so disgusting
I can tell this guy
Alright, I'm didn't like you have sisters like you've had sisters. Is that that's the vibe?
What a dope
Okay, oh my god, why is it always I don't I don't know it is like I know I used to think I was I was like
I don't we're supposed to it's like that. He's just I mean it's like he is I am it's not it's not just it's
Creepy is this like this creepy thing imagine saying they talk like saying that to somebody. Yeah, it's just disgusting. I
Mean I've said I know maybe inappropriate. I would make jokes like that
It's a big price
That's not good
You guys have be yeah, he's a big and patriot monster. I'm stuck
He has to be here, you know, he doesn't get this vegan patriot mod power just sets his own hacker
I know
Even I was like, you know, I was like, I'm not you know
Like the whole dick-pick thing was like not really to me. I was just I was just like a joke
I really didn't really care to see anybody's and it's like
Yeah, I
Mean I'm really I'm like if people say I'm like horny all about dick
I don't it's not hard for gay guys to find hookups, you know, it's like I could hook up with somebody
Probably as often as I wanted to but
because I can, I don't want to, because there's just a lot of promiscuity, diseases, and also not a lack of true love and affection in some of these hook-up relationships, and so...
Hi, babe. Hi. Hi, Lola.
Yeah.
I know Chris, I know Chris wasn't that sick and then he's, he's, and he's like, you know, complaining about saying I'm, I'm, I'm inappropriate. And then he's, he, he will say that too. So I don't understand.
I didn't say anything to Mr. Bigpipes. There was other people saying that to him. He's just, normal conversation is okay, but it's nothing. Yeah, it's nothing. It's just too weird, Mr. Bigpipes. It's too weird.
How many do go one and four hundred Wow?
I'm not one of them. I'm pretty flexible, but yeah, I think every guy has tried and I was not crystal
It's not it's not okay, but
All I can do is just kick them off the panel
you know, but I understand more like how
You know because now I'm getting the people in the panel saying outrageous things and it's like, I know it's it doesn't it's like
You want you just want to like take them off so I understand it but other people feel like
People talk to them and I'll be more mindful to keep people off or at least tell them to stop saying those things
Still time who are you and I see I don't know you guys see you on camera or something and waves me or
Tell me you are in the back chat or else. Maybe it's not the right night. He's stuck in making me. Okay, so let's see
Okay, you're waving okay, we'll see how this goes guys
Hello
Okay, well, it's okay
My kitty wants to interrogate you so tell me hello caller who are you from or where you're from and why are you calling? Good morning, Miguel?
Hey
You're not gonna form on me sir
But so I but so it's okay you're on camera anyway, so why does it matter? I have a background up, but you can't
Well, I'm sorry your microphone is bad, but thank you for coming bye
Well, I mean this gets weirder and weirder guys
Huh
Yeah, that was not a good not a great color. He did wave though. I didn't see him wave though
So I have your, I have your hand prints on file, I don't have the hand print, but I should figure that out how to do that though
Yeah, it's a terrible caller
Ah, what are you doing backstage? What are you doing? He's doing finger gestures at me
Let me see your face sir. Let me see your face reveal yourself
No one's gonna see. What are you doing backstage? Oh my god
Yeah, okay, so as a monotheist and having to be careful with any fooling you. Yeah, I know I
Know and yeah, I know as well Tom, but you were even cammed up. So why why would you want to be?
Put on camera so badly and why are you disguising your voice so ridiculously?
It's just on this question
Yeah, thank you sassy for what are you doing? What is what are you showing built on? What is that? Is that your dick?
He's showing some kind of weird photo. I don't know he left. Okay, never mind
Hi
Yeah, I don't know what's going
I mean, I think I am I sometimes a little slow, you know, but
I want my shit today
You know, it has it has been a crazy, you know, it's crazy a journey on YouTube so far
But the good thing is like
You know
If you get lost at sea or if you get if you off the course
You can always correct this you correct the sales
You get back on course, right?
Yeah, I mean and it's like there I just noticed there's a lot of like
Especially for the streamers, right? There's an audience for the streamers
Yeah, this should be like oh, I like this streamer, you know, who people think of the you know
Who like, you know, the PewDiePie and stuff like that. Oh, yeah, we'd like watching this streamer, right and then
Then this community like some of these communities like they don't like the stream
I mean they hate this they watch because I hate them and they want the they want to see them
Suffer and stuff and they just like oh like how do we torture them?
Psychologically like a lot of people some people think that is really it's really sick. I said, so what can I say?
What can I say to get a react? What can I say to bother? What can I say to scare?
It's all it is
Yeah, and so it's like it's just gotten so good. I thought oh, I'll write some rules up post the rules
Having rules it just makes people want to break if it is that it's laugh
It is that just makes them want to break them
So I guess that's why they keep doing it because I keep having to remind them
But because they don't listen you see it's like they need to live with psychology, right?
Some of the reasons I came over to stream actually to warn you. Yeah, I mean I can tell I can tell because like I just didn't know them very well
And then he's like, oh, it wasn't JT, it was Ziggy.
Ziggy comes over.
Oh, you know, I really like you
because they said you're a good guy.
And so I think you're cool now too.
I was like, okay, really?
I just am so skeptical about people that say they like me,
especially people that don't even know me.
And then I modded JT like twice.
And then,
Like the first time was like just right I prefer met him because like that's how I kind of am I just I
Kind of like liked him and so I've modded him and then
Everyone's like he's posting weird shit posting like weird shit
And so I am modern and then we're electro modern and then I remodeled him and then he started doing again
I'm modern and I also had to tell him several times don't use pictures in the thing. They're obviously
Because they're trying to
You know for my channel or just like not understanding or
There's trying to attack people through my channel either way
I'm not I'm not gonna be used condom for a bunch of people with a personal vendetta
I'm not part of it. See mr. Big Pies already said oh, I'm in their hands. Yeah, I know hands
You do my best to maintain
It's not fun. I also believe it's not it's a show. It's like, you know, it's a show. It's entertainment. It's the same at the end of the day
It's supposed we're supposed to be having fun here
It's not supposed to be all these hurt feelings angry people mad, you know, everyone's with the pitchforks and everyone's
accusing people and
There's million million gangs. It's like what?
What's going on?
Okay, they didn't understand what they're doing. You're right. They want to attack the channel and say
They went to attack other people while using your channel. That's exactly what to do. Yeah
Yeah, it seems like there's no reason. I just thinking other theories about why they're doing it to me. I
Personally think it's like some kind of homophobia
Because they're not interested in anything about I mean they get the big complementary terms the cats
But all of them have said we were just all of them have
And I don't care if you got to get it both on the wrong side of the bed or whatever and I didn't call you those names
Goddy, I didn't agree with anybody that called you name. I was just read I don't I was at the time
Only thing I was in the chat, so I think you just put your words my mouth
Collateral damage. Well, yeah, it's like, you know, not collateral damage
I'm a living breathing person with a life that is just trying to do my best and it's like really, you know, I haven't
Really accomplished very much in like a long time. And so it's like I am kind of like, you know
Proud of myself, you know, I'm kind of like, you know, at least
Being able to entertain a lot of people or some people or smile even a small amount of people I love that
Didn't do anything anybody and it's I I didn't I don't know who's who from where it's just too complicated. It's like so
I'm not I'm no I won't be collateral damage. Okay. I'll be the one. I'm the one that's protected by angels
Okay, I'll be the one that's like they're like, well, why that why didn't that work? Why is it?
I'm not I'm the one that's gonna make it. Okay
Okay, yeah.
It's the attitude, you never know, it's very easy,
it's really scary how easy it is for people to like,
you know, there's some good movies about conspiracies,
like one is what it's called, The Wicker Man.
It's a pretty good one.
This guy goes to investigate on an island.
There's no police force on the island,
but there's all these missing people starting to happen
on the island.
And so he goes to investigate.
And everyone on the island is kind of weird,
kind of a little bit cultish.
And then it was all a ruse just to trap them there.
I won't give away anything, but.
Yeah
Yeah, so I've been through some I've been through a lot of MK ultra stuff and
And you've been through a long time with you programming and it's not
It's not easy to
Well, just think cancer talking about it make it yeah
And I don't know we can watch movies backstage here if you guys are interested in watching a movie backstage
We have a movie night or something, but you can't watch stuff on the show. Hey, babe
It's like it's like if there's like a few you know if you actually have it I was actually like some kind of like
Like a Batman villain like you know, you know, and we're all going back and forth each other, but I'm just I'm just like a
Miss a kind person
Never I
Didn't I didn't do a bad thing to any of them, but but then all they can say is like, oh
He blocked me or he agreed with some comment or you know, I you know what I read comments
I read them out loud sometimes and I don't even read them beforehand
I had to stop myself because there's such crazy comments sometimes
Abandoned kindness wasn't that true of people but isn't that the saddest thing like I said it's like there's they're saying they say that
They say the bully they say pick on someone your own size, okay
It's like and maybe that can be a metaphor for pick on
Someone that's kind of doing the same thing. You're like, you know pick on pick on, you know, don't pick on some innocent person, right?
Pretty lame, right?
And that's why that's why there's what they're not allowed to kind that's why there's less kindness in the world than there should be because
There's this evil people that just like these be kindness of the weakness and they see you see
Love is dumb and they they they love conflict and chaos and hate. I can just tell I'm very familiar with stateness and
you know
somebody's different
Alternative religions so to speak in societies, right? I'm very familiar with them
I'll try to tell you about why this might be happening to me.
I'll give you a little astrological analysis about something in my chart.
Let me see if it makes sense, but I know it will come right up when I search for it.
Okay, so this says
It says a Saturn scapegoats and the blame game this is Capricorn
Some time ago I had a friend of mine and I were discussing the structure of a book
She was writing one of the books topics of expertise was patient rights
And we ended up discussing responsibilities of different parties involved and how this is seen by different groups in society
As soon as I hear the word structure and responsibility in the same conversation
I immediately think of Saturn my braids now programs. So that's all that's unavoidable for me. It can't be helped. I realized however
that by discussing the way this archetype can work in the real world, the information provides a new
way of structuring information. In this case, for a book, and generating new search areas.
As the planet Saturn has always been associated with the signed Capricorn,
and the traditional astrology with Aquarius before Uranus was discovered,
but since that is the topic for the next post we're getting ahead of ourselves,
we'll stick to the Capricorn style.
Saturn was pre- Uranus the last outer planet beyond that there was nothing so Saturn has to do with boundaries borders limits
Outside these limits was it is a scary unknown place
So Saturn always brings up fear fear of the unknown or going beyond our limits of our fixed patterns
But Saturn is also the wise old man and is therefore associated with teaching and learning life's sometimes hard lessons
He's associated with authority, someone who is earned place as a tribal elder through
experience and by getting older.
Saturn is highly visible in many traditional people, elderly people and scientists.
The way it works well in science is in the earthly providing side, structured experiments,
solid groundwork.
But it can lead to a fixility one sees in many elderly people who are both mentally and
physically inflexible.
Yes, this article will share it works. Okay, and it says an elderly astronomer had discovered that astrologers are having a Congress in the Astronomy Museum and
Okay, let me see. Well, maybe that wasn't the best thing but this one to read but that's the Capricorn's escape code. Let me see. Okay
Okay, Capricorn's case
Hey, what's up? What's up, babe? Yeah, it says anyone who's okay
And talk about scapegoats, okay
So if you're a scapegoat your achievements will be belittled minimize criticized and rejected
You are attacked and disbelieved if you tell the truth and blow the whistle on negative and inappropriate
Dynamics revealed dreaded secrets
you may be held responsible for conflicts of the family
and be blamed for the actions of others.
You will feel like a black sheep of the family.
No one feels this way for nothing.
You may be the healthiest family member,
but are always accused of being sick and bad.
You might occupy the role of family outcast
and are treated with disdain or disgust by family
or maybe even by yourself.
You find yourself consistently being accused
of only caring about yourself.
Being thoughtless and selfish and never measuring up to expectations set which you know couldn't be further from the truth
you're held responsible for
The problems conflicts or challenges even if they have nothing to do with you other people blame you for their actions
You might end up feeling a bit of shame for being the bad guy and anger for being blamed for the negative dynamics
Anyway
It's gonna be has been your doll the crystal
She'll eventually see through that. Yeah
You know that guy Carl he
pulls knives out scare humans and animals
It's weird
They caught my pipe say pipe said
Tiffany where's oh my god
I'm not gonna repeat that
And
He imagine a ten you know what a handful of ten is I mean
Plus it's like too perfect. I
Don't think there's very many tens. I think most people are like 9.9
The blackout poor mom psyche. Yes, he did. Oh, I did he hold on. Well, he was he didn't but he was
He was being impolite and then he kept switching his his profile photo and I don't know why so I
Asked him not to do it and he kept doing it. So
I'm in the dark, alone, with you.
I've seen this before.
That's a good song.
So it's called by the birthday master.
I'll sing it for you.
That's not too long.
If I can remember the lyrics.
Actually was on his live when he said he should shed poor mom psyche. I said I
Told him that I modded for you enough to do that
Yeah, I ran to my Trident's chat and he called me at F-A-G-G-O-T there
Yeah, there's guys notes planner in the chat like really like we this like we need to start I think maybe
There's like specific stuff said I just I don't want it in my chat, right?
Yeah, we heard about all the discourse stuff, you know, I
I would I
Was listening very carefully, you know
Sometimes when people don't think I'm not not watching I am and
Sometimes what I'm not talking there's a reason right?
We're bringing kindness back guys guys guys. I know I have so many good people here that like, you know
If we we all put our heads together like it was with good energy and good intentions and
I believe that
I believe that love will always overcome hate
Imagine people that I just I know these groups. I was I watched 90 day fiance like I watched religiously for years, right?
and on
YouTube, there's a huge 90 day fiancee commentary channel thing, there's like a thousand commentary
channels.
So I would watch some of those.
They were going through the shit, all the same shit.
And even worse, I mean, they found these private Facebook groups of other shivers are all trying to take each other down. They were sending the kids, people's kids photos and the rest of the nurse school.
This is the most disgusting thing. It's so crazy. You know, it's just for just because other person had a channel that covered 90 Day Fiance, right?
So I can get crazy, right?
Yeah, B. B. It's like, you know, guys, that's what happens.
It can like when conspiracy start, it's like, you know, the rabbit hole gets deeper and deeper.
Oh, well, it actually, it's like, you know, it's like, it can go on forever with all these
speculation. That's why it's kind of like, don't put your energy into like the rabbit holes.
It feels like different characters and people, even people aren't
It's called improv just to improv post link. Okay, got you Joker do improv and you know play along
You're awake. Okay good. I want up Joker
I'm not jelly of you mr. Big pipes you played
Guys, what was that was that Beatles song he played for like an hour? I
Can't believe it's not still bringing it through my head. It was just never ending
But I I fuck leave this room. I like your like your music, but
It's hard to hear you can't you just wouldn't stop playing
Okay, mr. Big Pipes, mr. Big Pipes you accuse me of being the enemy's hands. I mean
How insulting can I can you get?
That's like you're like the fifth person to assault me. So I'm a little patience for right now
Trying to have a nice and then I know I got my
My my joke were coming up
I'm holding it. I'm going to be talking to him for a minute.
There you go, Lincoln's Pins.
You look for some reaction like you're proud.
Yeah, I mean, I love Priscilla too.
Uh-oh.
Midnight, don't you dare threaten me.
Hey, what up, man?
My name is Pau Ru, man.
What up, man?
Hi, Pau Ru.
Who this is?
This is Dignisa.
This is...
Actually, Arthur's Dignisa.
You remember Dignisa?
Who this is?
My name is Pau Ru.
So, you know, you said, you said, if Joke comes on, I swear to God, like, and so, but there's always jokes coming on. Oh, yeah. Oh, okay.
What's up, my friend?
Hey, man, let me tell you something real quick, man. I run this shit, man. Like, you know what I'm saying? Type shit, man. Type shit.
What do you run?
Run this shit man type shit. Oh, wait, you're like my you're on my panel
No, I run this shit man. Joker. I need to power room man. What you talking about man?
You know who the fuck I am man
Are you piranha and?
Some other women some guy with the initials rule daughter or son
For you. Yes. You're just you're just my choker turn on a light. All right. Yes, I
Can't see are you nude? I
Hope you are I'm just kidding. No, okay. Okay. Well, that didn't go well. I don't know. He's not it wasn't like that
That's not one of my favorite characters. I like what he's like the owner of Streamy are better than
His accent. Oh, here he is. Hi
Opening the warrants. Oh, I can see me right? Yeah
You just have to take this golf club
I don't work
I should see him. You're right
That's here. Mr. Big. I'm not terrified of you. It's just I'm talking to the Joker right now and
All you're all you're doing is whining about me
Mr. Big Pipes and saying that I'm like a bad person
Blaming me for for people saying something about you. I can't like I can't take it right now
You know a lot of people are terrified of mr. Big Pipes because of his talents
Yeah, I mean
All right, I'm afraid it'll pee in my in my jugs throughout
Yeah
I have actually I'm charging my phone so I have this new light if you see my new lights pretty cool
I'll pull it. I'll give that one to you. You should turn the light on dude. Here comes. Yeah
You like you're gonna tell spooky stories in the dark. Look at this. There you go. That's like schooler
Cool. I have to put on one color though
Like I'm sitting on Jupiter, you know what the morning time right now. Mm-hmm. It's 449 LA
So what is your show about now my show is about
It's about
My show is about it's always been about me tarot cats and
Open panels
where anything can happen.
So it's a variety show, but I'm retooling a few things.
I mean, I'm gonna be shortening the time I'm on.
I'm gonna be dedicating, like,
probably like the first hour of the show
just to doing readings.
And before I start a panel and the show starts,
I'm gonna...
You know, I'm gonna so you know, it might some of these things mine up. I'm experimenting. That's why I've been on so much
I've just been seeing what what works what time and stuff
Thinking about it and so mix your men sing and I
Mr. Bigfoot, I'm talking to Joker right now and Mr. Bigfoot all you do is wine up right now
All right, why need to that and you've tried like 20 shots of vodka. I think I think I don't think it's the best time
I'm trying to
Trying to talk to my man here. Okay
Yeah, and so I'll do my I can do like stuff on a backup my backup channel. I can like, you know
Because if we wanted to go extra over longer after the show we can do
extended panels or maybe karaoke and stuff on the other channels is not monetized so I can do all that stuff there and
So yeah, so my show is just about my show is just about basically
Me and everyone having fun and as long as I'm I'm me and most people are having fun. I'm doubting to my show
It's not fun for me. You know
Things happen in life where you walk away from things that you know, even that one time made you happy
But I'm confident. I'll be able to get things in the right track if I'm not, you know
What happens happens. It's called pragmatism. It's like
Whatever will be will be case of ross or all right
Bet it you know if there are just like some people are just like, you know, they just want to like spoil
There's something called happiness haters
They see happiness in somebody they see somebody that has good energy to warm that is friendly and is light
And then they're like they want to
That person thinks they're perfect and that person thinks they're better than a person has they think there's something
I'm gonna prove that I'm gonna prove them and everything
I'll be real with you a lot of the people that you associate with
like Black RG, KZ, Queen, Elizabeth, Alisson's band from the show now.
A lot of those guys will flip on a switch as soon as someone's happy.
Aldo, all of them. All the no-camera people.
Well, there's no camera has been a problem. I mean, I mean, so most of these people have been
unmodded. If they, because I have noticed a few, like some of them have kind of like disobeyed.
Um, and I think all of them have basically good hearts and you know, something's gonna be good and I believe
Where people are good and bad, but I don't I don't know. It's like
Even that thing back on sick was like trying to like say he was gonna on a live of stuff on a panel and stuff like that tonight
I mean, it's just like this
He's trying to get help you trying to use you to yell
Well, I hope so
I did tell them not to do it when I restarted the stream,
but I don't want people saying they're gonna live
themselves on my stream, first of all.
And then second of all, it's not the black, okay, hold on.
Who's this?
Is that you, Amanda, in backstage, or no?
No, I don't think it's Amanda, okay, okay, okay.
Guys backstage, just go outside the studio.
You guys, go hail an Uber, bye.
Yeah, okay, so, yeah.
Uh
Yeah, I don't know I'm fine. It's just it's just like wow it's like, you know
It's some there's some periods of time where it's just like man. It's like everyone
everyone friend and I mean
Everyone everyone's hitting hitting me and saying bad things and it's like okay. Well, nobody likes me then
I'm just confused some of the time because that's like people feel mad at me for stuff that I really
had nothing to do with or even
Remember half the time and so I don't know if they're like throwing me saying trying to make you feel bad or
Because most of the people they don't think people I've heard people say much worse things than I've
than other people and that they're friends with
No, I'm paying for a piece of the chat to the panel too, but the chat is there are like 20,000 messages in chat
So I missed most of the chat anyway
I do try and keep because there are people telling me things like hey, you're being porn bombers of or hey
You know, I get some feedback. It's interesting
It's not good and I'll be a lot of friends
You need to close your eyes and you need to just meditate
Okay, yeah, Joker
Please please
I admit it. I know how to close my eyes. I know how to take deep breaths. I know how I sleep. I slept well
I'm fine. I'm talking calm. I'm just expressing myself. I I don't like to be told to I need to relax
You need to listen to what everyone tells you to do and do exactly what they
I do well, that's it. That's not your recipe for disaster, right?
How about how about I just do what I want to do and then at the end of the day? Hey, I'll face the consequences of my deal
At least I did what I want
Rather than I'm just gonna be living fear of every single like little asshole in the world that wants to scare me, right?
And then there's plenty of them, right?
Yeah, he's pretty he's pretty lame, you know, I love when people that are not even
A monetized channel or I think he's healthy. I think that's why I mean God
I let I let him on my panel. I let him you know
Posts link if he wants to I mean I all I can do is like, you know, I
You know say hey, hey, you know, let them on the panel even though he was rude to me
I let him on the panel. I didn't ever try to hurt him. I don't understand
People are so smug been dealing with me. It's like
Like I like I'm just like some
So what it is that you're getting used right I'll explain to you people use you so they can they pretend to be your friends
So they can come on here and talk shit, but then as soon as they get tired of you
They're like fuck you bye
Well, good. I'm glad I'm glad they get tired me. They can't think I don't really I don't care like really what breeze people like here
It's like if they'd like me or whatever if they want to talk shit or whatever
I mean, there's a time and place for both of those but it's just like it's just
you should basically
Like me, you know if you don't like me the wire like go go touch it somewhere else
I mean
It's just like stop the some energies around fighting and then created the touch the community you create like
Oh, I created. Oh, okay. Well, Joker. Well, yeah, thanks. Well, thanks for your thanks for your opinion, but it's like who cares
I get I created my show. Look, I have I forget but can show this it's doing fine
It's like I if I have a problem with it, I'm just gonna do with you, you know, just not have you just condescending it by
Okay, I created a car. Oh, what a gang was fake myself because I created a toxic community
I am I responsible for people's toxicity. I'm responsible for, you know
Okay who showed up in the chat maybe to some extent I you know put to some areas but
it's other people you know it's like it's everybody it's everybody you know it's not just me
creating the community I don't I don't drag people in here people come here and whoever comes here comes right so
Yeah
I don't know. I'm just so sick of being lectured and told what I need to do what I should do
It's like and you know that and so you know, you know, you should you're like, you know, you shouldn't like be
saying those things I'm bugging maybe but
Yeah, but what guys why you put my buttons when you I'm not gonna like
That's just because I was just throwing you dude. Just calm just okay. Yeah
Joker first of all, I didn't raise the guy did I raise my voice at all? Did I I don't think I raised my voice at all
So stop it Joker. You know, I'm not them. Not them. Don't play with me Joker. Don't play with me
Don't want to hide you
Hey
I'm your mommy
Joker I'm your step mommy ready to step
No customary. Oh my gosh, my voice is so bad. I
Think I'm gonna
Take a winner cry
Joker stop
My feelings are hurt
Don't make your brother be you up my feelings are hurt
You know you're gonna drop brother is gonna fuck you up. I
Don't know which one of you are older
But you're about to both get your asses spiked
Well, you could smoke break for a second. Joker. I miss ya. Calm down. I
Know Joker. It's like I've been up all night. You see these propane tinks. I
Have no air left in my nostril
Like my nostril broken, you know that
You know how it feels your nostrils broken what happened?
Well, I got into it doesn't matter. Okay. I'm sorry. I don't mean to be personal. Yeah
It is it's it is what it is. I was at a rack and like I feel like it's broken
Well, I think it probably would be
A lot of pain or really notice them broken, but well my wife's pretty noticeable
Lee it was at the time, you know my whole face swelled up, so I mean it was broken at the time
I went to the hospital. It was a whole thing. I did a whole recovery
She used to be a hand model if you didn't know that oh my god
She I got seen pictures of her hand on like magazines
No
Her she has to be a hand model like her hand is like sexy, I guess
She has a good-looking hand
How does one become a hand model
Because one becomes something else
How do I become my in-model, Chris and Marie?
Get a job.
How do I become my in-model, though?
Go to college.
Whether it's a college career for modeling?
Not exactly. I mean, there is, but it's called, like...
Arts and music and arts you can go to I
Don't know you're in
Right you're in Georgia. Yeah
Yeah
Yeah, you could do well go to cosmetology
Why would I do that?
Are you drunk or not working on your own and you drunk doing your own shit work on your own fucking face
Work on your own shit. You become your own drunk. Are you drunk right now?
I'm tired dude. Why are you awake if you're tired?
Because I think close your eyes right now. My eyes are closed. My eyes been closed
Now breathe and
Rub your hands all over your body while you breathe. Okay, stop it. Now you went too far. Now you went too far
I'm just kidding. I'm not I'm smoking. Are you smoking this morning crystal? Are you smoking cigarettes?
Nothing. No
Look at my boys like
About to die, dude
When you drink crystal, how many cigarettes do you smoke?
How many cigarettes do you smoke?
Depends but under a pack, but it doesn't even matter. It's it's the alcohol
It does something to my deviated septum
Where it closes it so it cuts all the air breathing off
Or I'm allergic to alcohol or something. So it cuts all the breathing off
So yeah, it's really hard for me to breathe as soon as I take a
drink
Rock on
Yeah, I understand so I think I made psych match, so I
Was just trolling but like sometimes if you come on here and you start like demanding him to do something
Or tell him what to do so many people tell him what to do than now
It triggers them so I
Feel bad. I didn't mean to trigger. I
Don't think you did
He was being sassy. Yes, I don't think you did
Sometimes you know not everybody can take a joke at all times, you know
Joker, you know, uh
How many times I scratched your fucking face off and, um
Redrew it and it was still a joke
You hurt my feelings
Remember when I drew you crystal and you demanded that you eat it
Yeah
Because I want to eat the fucking paper you want to make me look like see better eat that shit
You want to make me look like that you better eat that you better do it you better do it now
Sorry about that, buddy. Sorry. I made you eat paper
Hey, what's up pussy? Um fuck your shit nigger nigger nigger nigger. Oh my god
He ruined everything like